Guide to the Robert J. Levine Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1955-2014; Accession 2016-M-0064; 9.78; (22 boxes)
  - Office files
    - Merck Research Laboratories, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Messenger, Arlene, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Metz, Stewart A., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Milwaukee Medical College of Wisconsin, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Minority Health Office, Department of Health and Human Services, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Mirkin, Bernard, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Mitchell, William, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Morton-Ranney, Robert W., 1987–1991 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Mount Sinai School of Medicine, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Multiple Sclerosis: A Global Perspective, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Murphy, Timothy, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute, 2002–2012 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute bronchoscopy workshop, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - National Human Research Protections Advisory Committee, Office for Human Research Protections, Department of Health and Human Services, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - National Institute of Environmental Health Sciences, 2011–2012 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - National Research Council, 2012–2014 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Nellie Westerman Prize for Research in Ethics, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Nellie Westerman Prize for Research in Ethics, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Nellie Westerman Prize for Research in Ethics, 1976–1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Nellie Westerman Prize for Research in Ethics, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Nellie Westerman Prize for Research in Ethics, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - New Clinical Drug Evaluation Unit, National Institute of Mental Health, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - New Haven Lawn Club Association, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Academy of Sciences Membership, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Newman, Andrew B., letter of recommendation, Circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Ngugi, Elizabeth, University of Nairobi, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Notecards, Circa 1960s (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Notes, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Office for Human Research Protections, United States Department of Health and Human Services, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Office of Research on Women's Health, National Institute of Health, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Papyrus Institute, Circa 1990s (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - People to People Ambassador Program, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Pfizer consultation, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Pinto, Harlan, 1983–2008 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Portugal, 1987–1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Prusoff, William, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Public Responsibility in Medicine and Research, 1979–2013 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Public Responsibility in Medicine and Research, faculty resource, compact disc, 2012; 1 (Box 21)
    - Public Responsibility in Medicine and Research, Investigator 101: Training for investigators in the responsible conduct of human subjects research, compact disc, 2002; 1 (Box 22)
    - The Publicizing of Biomedical Research: The Ethical Dance Between Scientists and the Media conference, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Puerto Rico, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Quigley, Kathleen, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Reader's Digest, Circa 1960s (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Research Ethics course, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Research Ethics working group, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Roddey, Angela, Circa 1980s (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Rudich, Lynn Karen, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Russia trip, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Saybrook College, Yale University, 2008–2012 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Schell Center for International Human Rights, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Scherling-Plough, 2007–2008 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Scientific American magazine, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Sessions, Rose Marie, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Seton Hall University, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Sheridan, Edythe, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Sirota, Roberta A., 1972–1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Skiing, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Sloane, David, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Smith, David, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Social Security, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - South West Airlines, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Sprumont, Dominique, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Staff salaries, 1968–1983 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Stereo, Circa 1990s (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Student demonstrations and protests, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Student Faculty Advisory Program, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Student guests, 1990–1998 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Student recommendations, 1965–1974 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Student support group, 1977–1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Ten Commandments, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Third World Conference on Bioethics, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - University of California, Davis, 2002–2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - University of California, San Francisco Medical Center, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - University of Kansas, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Vann, Richard, 1990–1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Walbert, Ruth E., resume, Circa 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Weed, Matthew, 1999–2000 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Whitney, Robin, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Woods, Scott, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Work, Jeffrey William, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Yager, Robert D., 1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Yale University, appointment as instructor in medicine, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Yale University, Clinical Investigation Committee, 1969–1971 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
    - Yale University, Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 2008–2009 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Yale University, Interdisciplinary Center for Bioethics executive committee meeting, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Yale Pediatric Ethics Committee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Yale University Pharmacology, 1965–1981 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Yale University Physician Associate Students, clinical research paper reviews, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Yale University School of Medicine, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)